Guide to the Antiquarian bookseller catalog collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- F
  - X346 F872, 1971; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Samuel T. Freeman Co.; Philadelphia, PA. (Box 569, Folder 3777)
  - X346 F8775, undated; nos. 1-135, 3 catalogs
    - Freeman Library Service; New York, N. Y. (Box 569, Folder 3778)
  - X346 F889, 1937-undated; nos. 6-19, 10 catalogs
    - Franco American Book Company; New York City, N. Y. (Box 570, Folder 3779)
  - X346 F889 I, 1943 - 1949; nos. 1-18, 19 catalogs
    - French Book Corporation; New York, N. Y. (Box 570, Folder 3780-3781)
  - X346 F893, undated; nos. 12-19, 7 catalogs
    - J. Fricelli Associates; Brooklyn, N. Y. (Box 570, Folder 3782)
  - X346 F91, 1923 - 1932; nos.1-43, 43 catalogs
    - Edward George Friehold; London (Box 570, Folder 3783-3785)
    - Edward George Friehold; London (Box 571, Folder 3786)
  - X346 F917, 1939 - 1954; unnumbered, 9 catalogs
    - C. E. Fritzes Hovbokhandel; Stockholm (Box 571, Folder 3787-3788)
  - X346 F917 I, 1911; nos. 2-8, 7 catalogs
    - C. E. Fritzes Hovbokhandel; Stockholm (Box 571, Folder 3789)
  - X346 F917 II, 1949 - 1950; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - C. E. Fritzes Hovbokhandel; Stockholm (Box 571, Folder 3790)
  - X346 F922, 1966 - 1985; nos. 3-77, 16 catalogs
    - Frognal Rare Books; London, England (Box 571, Folder 3791-3793)
- G
  - X346 G1287, 1929 - 1955; nos. 11-91, 31 catalogs
    - Librairie Gallimard; Paris (Box 572, Folder 3794-3796)
  - X346 G13, undated; nos. 25-213, 64 catalogs
    - Galloway Porter, LTD.; Cambridge, England (Box 572, Folder 3797-3799)
    - Galloway Porter, LTD.; Cambridge, England (Box 573, Folder 3800-3802)
  - X346 G13 I, 1953 - 1970; nos. 54-69, 9 catalogs
    - Galloway Porter, LTD.; Cambridge, England (Box 573, Folder 3803)
  - X346 G147, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Gammel Book Company; Austin, Texas (Box 573, Folder 3804)
  - X346 G155, 1949 - 1960; nos. 1-34, 19 catalogs
    - Eric H. Ganley; Forest Hills, N. Y. (Box 573, Folder 3805-3806)
  - X346 G168, 1812 - 1813; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - W. Gardiner; London (Box 574, Folder 3807)
  - X346 G1835, 1966 - 1978; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - Garisenda Antiquariato; Bologna (Box 574, Folder 3808-3810)
  - X346 G186, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - H. B. Garner; Philadelphia, PA. (Box 574, Folder 3811)
  - X346 G188, undated; no. 22, 1 catalog
    - Joseph Garnier; St. Louis, MO. (Box 574, Folder 3812)
  - X346 G193, 1854; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Garrigue Christern; New York (Box 574, Folder 3813)
  - X346 G192, 1934; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - G. Blanchfield; [Hartford, Conn.?] (Box 574, Folder 3814)
  - X346 G225, undated; no. 13, 5 catalog
    - Ernest R. Gee; New York (Box 574, Folder 3815)
  - X346 G27, 1889 - 1913; nos. 89-361, 50 catalogs
    - Adolf Geering; Basel (Box 574, Folder 3816)
    - Adolf Geering; Basel (Box 575, Folder 3817-3821)
    - Adolf Geering; Basel (Box 576, Folder 3822-3824)
  - X346 G274, 1925 - 1929; nos. 1-5, 5 catalogs
    - Rudolf Geering; Basel (Box 576, Folder 3825)
    - Rudolf Geering; Basel (Box 577, Folder 3826-3827)
  - X346 G29, 1876 - 1986; nos. 58-687, 357 catalogs
    - William George; England (Box 578, Folder 3828-3833)
    - William George; England (Box 579, Folder 3834-3838)
    - William George; England (Box 580, Folder 3839-3844)
    - William George; England (Box 581, Folder 3845-3850)
    - William George; England (Box 582, Folder 3851-3856)
    - William George; England (Box 583, Folder 3857-3862)
    - William George; England (Box 584, Folder 3863)
  - X346 G29 I, 1933 - 1940; unnumbered, 9 catalogs
    - William George; England (Box 584, Folder 3864-3865)
  - X346 G295, 1910 - 1955; nos. 164-396, 275 catalogs
    - George Gregory; Bath (Box 584, Folder 3866-3868)
    - George Gregory; Bath (Box 585, Folder 3869-3874)
    - George Gregory; Bath (Box 586, Folder 3875-3879)
    - George Gregory; Bath (Box 587, Folder 3880-3885)
    - George Gregory; Bath (Box 588, Folder 3886-3888)
  - X346 G295 II, 1948-1962, undated; nos. 5-34, 13 catalogs
    - George Bayntun; Bath (Box 588, Folder 3889-3890)
  - X346 G33 I, 1906 - 1964; nos. 1-175, 146 catalogs
    - Paul Geuthner; Paris (Box 588, Folder 3891-3892)
    - Paul Geuthner; Paris (Box 589, Folder 3893-3898)
    - Paul Geuthner; Paris (Box 590, Folder 3899-3904)
    - Paul Geuthner; Paris (Box 591, Folder 3905-3910)
    - Paul Geuthner; Paris (Box 592, Folder 3911-3916)
  - X346 G33 II, 1924 - 1940; nos. 8-71, 57 catalogs
    - Paul Geuthner; Paris (Box 592, Folder 3917)
    - Paul Geuthner; Paris (Box 593, Folder 3918-3919)
  - X346 G338, 1961 - 1969; nos. 40-74, 26 catalogs
    - H. Geyer; Austria (Box 593, Folder 3920-3923)
    - H. Geyer; Austria (Box 594, Folder 3924)
  - X346 G374, 1907; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Henry March Gilbert Son; Southampton (Box 594, Folder 3925)
  - X346 G375, undated; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Richard Gilbertson; London (Box 594, Folder 3926)
  - X346 G39, undated; nos. 26-241, 5 catalogs
    - Gilhofer Ranschburg; Vienne (Box 594, Folder 3927)
  - X346 G4215, 1946-1947, undated; nos. 25-68, 6 catalogs
    - Stanley Gilman; N. Y. C. (Box 594, Folder 3928)
  - X346 G4216, 1916 - 1964; nos. 4-140, 28 catalogs
    - Clarence Gilman; Crompond, New York (Box 594, Folder 3929-3931)
  - X346 G4295, 1966-undated; nos. 1-15, 13 catalogs
    - Bruce Gimelson; Fort Washington, Penna. (Box 594, Folder 3932)
    - Bruce Gimelson; Fort Washington, Penna. (Box 595, Folder 3933)
  - X346 G4422, 1809; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Pierre Giraud; Turin (Box 595, Folder 3934)
  - X346 G4695, 1910; no. 17, 1 catalog
    - И. ГЛАЗУНОВА (Box 595, Folder 3935)
  - X346 G53, 1925 - 1929; nos. 3-36, 4 catalogs
    - Louis Godefroy; Paris (Box 595, Folder 3936)
  - X346 G53 I, 1908 - 1938; nos. 71-77, 2 catalogs
    - Pierre Godefroy; Paris (Box 595, Folder 3937)
  - X346 G53 II, 1924 - 1933; nos. 26-56, 18 catalogs
    - Pierre Godefroy; Paris (Box 595, Folder 3938-3939)
  - X346 G53 III, 1921-1946, undated; nos. 1-39, 15 catalogs
    - Pierre Godefroy; Paris (Box 595, Folder 3940)
  - X346 G53 IV, 1956; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Pierre Godefroy; Paris (Box 596, Folder 3941)
  - X346 G54, 1920 - 1975; nos. 71-275, 212 catalogs
    - T. C. Godfrey; York, England (Box 596, Folder 3942-3947)
    - T. C. Godfrey; York, England (Box 597, Folder 3948-3953)
    - T. C. Godfrey; York, England (Box 598, Folder 3954-3959)
    - T. C. Godfrey; York, England (Box 599, Folder 3960-3964)
  - X346 G54 I, 1947; no. 111, 1 catalog
    - Thomas C. Godfrey; York, England (Box 599, Folder 3965)
  - X346 G556, undated; nos. 1051-1053, 2 catalogs
    - Max Götz; München (Box 599, Folder 3966)
  - X346 G566, 1952 - 1954; nos. 42-60, 8 catalogs
    - Walter Goldberg Books; New York, N. Y. (Box 599, Folder 3967)
  - X346 G57, undated; nos. 1-166, 169 catalogs
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 599, Folder 3968)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 600, Folder 3969-3973)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 601, Folder 3974-3978)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 602, Folder 3979-3984)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 603, Folder 3985-3990)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 604, Folder 3991-3997)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 605, Folder 3998-4003)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 606, Folder 4004-4009)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 607, Folder 4010-4013)
  - X346 G57 I, undated; nos. 1-33, 25 catalogs
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 607, Folder 4014)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt Co. LTD.; London (Box 608, Folder 4015-4016)
  - X346 G5725, undated-1980; nos. 25-111, 61 catalogs
    - Lucien Goldschmidt; New York, N. Y. (Box 608, Folder 4017-4020)
    - Lucien Goldschmidt; New York, N. Y. (Box 609, Folder 4021-4024)
  - X346 G58, undated; nos. 1-3, 3 catalogs
    - Edward Goldston Son LTD.; London (Box 609, Folder 4025)
  - X346 G589, 1966-1974; nos. 2-107, 53 catalogs
    - L. Gonnelli Figli; Firenze (Box 609, Folder 4026-4027)
    - L. Gonnelli Figli; Firenze (Box 610, Folder 4028-4033)
  - X346 G589 I, 1977 - 1986; nos. 9-27, 12 catalogs
    - L. Gonnelli Figli; Firenze (Box 611, Folder 4034-4039)
  - X346 G62, 1900 - 1986; nos. 2-599, 574 catalogs
    Bound volumes
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 611, Folder 4040)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 612, Folder 4041-4046)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 613, Folder 4047-4052)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 614, Folder 4053-4059)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 615, Folder 4060-4065)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 616, Folder 4066-4071)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 617, Folder 4072-4077)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 618, Folder 4078-4083)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 619, Folder 4084-4089)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 620, Folder 4090-4095)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 621, Folder 4096-4101)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 622, Folder 4102-4107)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 623, Folder 4108-4113)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 624, Folder 4114-4119)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 625, Folder 4120-4125)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 626, Folder 4126-4132)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 627, Folder 4133-4139)
  - X346 G62 I, 1929 - 1986; unnumbered, 111 catalogs
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 628, Folder 4140-4143)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 629, Folder 4144-4147)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 630, Folder 4148-4150)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 631, Folder 4151-4155)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 632, Folder 4156-4162)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 633, Folder 4163-4165)
  - X346 G62 II, 1941 - 1986; unnumbered, 78 catalogs
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 633, Folder 4166-4169)
  - X346 G62 A, 1921 - 1929; unnumbered, 14 catalogs
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 634, Folder 4170)
  - X346 G62 B, undated; nos. 1-10, 10 catalogs
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 634, Folder 4171)
  - X346 G67, 1913 - 1930; nos. 3-38, 29 catalogs
    - Herbert E. Gorfin; Lewisham (Box 634, Folder 4172-4173)
  - X346 G7115, 1964 - 1970; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    - Gotham Book Mart; New York, N. Y. (Box 634, Folder 4174)
  - X346 G7125, 1963 - 1968; nos. 374-401, 5 catalogs
    - Paul Gothier; Liege, Belgique (Box 634, Folder 4175)
  - X346 G7125 I, 1968; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Paul Gothier; Liege, Belgique (Box 634, Folder 4176)
  - X346 G7157 I, undated; nos. 1-35, 22 catalogs
    - Ernest E. Gottlieb; Beverly Hills, California (Box 635, Folder 4177-4178)
  - X346 G717 VI, 1941 - 1951; nos. 2, 4-7, 5 catalogs
    - Paul Gottschalk, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 635, Folder 4179)
  - X346 G747, 1851 - 1866; nos. 10-24, 10 catalogs
    - Gowans; New York, N. Y. (Box 635, Folder 4180-4181)
  - X346 G749, undated; nos. 1-80, 59 catalogs
    - B. M. E. De Graaf; Nieuwkoop, Netherlands (Box 635, Folder 4182-4183)
    - B. M. E. De Graaf; Nieuwkoop, Netherlands (Box 636, Folder 4184-4189)
    - B. M. E. De Graaf; Nieuwkoop, Netherlands (Box 637, Folder 4190-4194)
  - X346 G749 II, 1975 - 1978; unnumbered, 5 catalogs
    - B. M. E. De Graaf; Nieuwkoop, Netherlands (Box 637, Folder 4195)
  - X346 G75, 1919 - 1959; nos. 3-305, 213 catalogs
    - Grafton Co.; London (Box 637, Folder 4196)
    - Grafton Co.; London (Box 638, Folder 4197-4203)
    - Grafton Co.; London (Box 639, Folder 4204-4209)
    - Grafton Co.; London (Box 640, Folder 4210-4216)
    - Grafton Co.; London (Box 641, Folder 4217-4220)
  - X346 G759, undated; no. 15, 1 catalog
    - A. S. Graig; London (Box 641, Folder 4221)
  - X346 G7592, 1941 - 1978; nos. 1-143, 103 catalogs
    - Gramercy Book Shop; New York, N. Y. (Box 641, Folder 4222)
    - Gramercy Book Shop; New York, N. Y. (Box 642, Folder 4223-4228)
    - Gramercy Book Shop; New York, N. Y. (Box 643, Folder 4229-4234)
  - X346 G7595, 1967 - 1969; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - E. Granata; Milano (Box 643, Folder 4235)
  - X346 G76, 1949; nos. 1, 1 catalog
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 644, Folder 4236)
  - X346 G76 I, 1895 - 1956; unnumbered, 38 catalogs
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 644, Folder 4237-4242)
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 645, Folder 4243-4246)
  - X346 G76 II, 1887 - 1957; unnumbered, 221 catalogs
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 645, Folder 4247)
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 646, Folder 4248-4253)
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 647, Folder 4254-4259)
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 648, Folder 4260-4266)
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 649, Folder 4267-4272)
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 650, Folder 4273-4278)
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 651, Folder 4279-4282)
  - X346 G76 III, 1884 - 1984; unnumbered, 109 catalogs
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 651, Folder 4283-4284)
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 652, Folder 4285-4290)
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 653, Folder 4291-4293)
  - X346 G76 IV, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - John Grant Booksellers LTD.; Edinburgh (Box 653, Folder 4294)
  - X346 G792, 1883-[1909]; nos. 10-278 + Misc., 91 catalogs
    - Henry Gray; London, England (Box 653, Folder 4295-4297)
    - Henry Gray; London, England (Box 654, Folder 4298-4301)
  - X346 G792 II, undated; nos. 9-35, 15 catalogs
    - Henry Gray; London, England (Box 654, Folder 4302-4303)
  - X346 G792 III, undated; nos. 10-15, 11 catalogs
    - Henry Gray; London, England (Box 654, Folder 4304)
  - X346 G792 IV, undated; nos. 1-2, 2 catalogs
    - Henry Gray; London, England (Box 655, Folder 4305)
  - X346 G822, 1944 - 1969; nos. 22-106, 27 catalogs
    - The Green Book Shop; New York, N. Y. (Box 655, Folder 4306-4308)
  - X346 G8267, 1965 - 1986; nos. 1-47, 34 catalogs
    - Falkner Greirson; Dublin, Ireland (Box 655, Folder 4309-4312)
    - Falkner Greirson; Dublin, Ireland (Box 656, Folder 4313-4315)
  - X346 G8267 I, undated; no. 5-19, 4 catalogs
    - Falkner Greirson; Dublin, Ireland (Box 656, Folder 4316)
  - X346 G8267 II, 1976; nos. 7-8, 2 catalogs
    - Falkner Greirson; Dublin, Ireland (Box 656, Folder 4317)
  - X346 G8625, undated; nos. 5-52, 26 catalogs
    - K. Gregory; New York, N. Y. (Box 656, Folder 4318-4319)
    - K. Gregory; New York, N. Y. (Box 657, Folder 4320)
  - X346 G8754, 1952 - 1958; nos. 8-19, 10 catalogs
    - Griffin Bookshop; New York, N. Y. (Box 657, Folder 4321)
  - X346 G8765, 1967 - 1972; nos. 1-22, 11 catalogs
    - Gian Carlo Grifoni; Bologna (Box 657, Folder 4322)
  - X346 G885, undated; nos. 1-15, 14 catalogs
    - Paul Grinke; London (Box 657, Folder 4323-4324)
  - X346 G8851, undated; nos. 1-4, 4 catalogs
    - Grinke and Rodgers; London (Box 657, Folder 4325-4326)
  - X346 G8985, undated; nos. 40-120, 20 catalogs
    - Grønholt Pedersens Boghus; Copenhagen, Denmark (Box 658, Folder 4327-4331)
  - X346 G914, undated; nos. 10-27, 9 catalogs
    - Bernard Gross; London (Box 658, Folder 4332-4333)
  - X346 G9185, 1953 - 1957; nos. 1-5, 5 catalogs
    - Un Groupe de Libraires Parisiens; Paris (Box 659, Folder 4334-4335)
  - X346 G922, 1898 - 1951; nos. 18-198, unnumbered, 71 catalogs
    - Ernest Gründ; Paris (Box 659, Folder 4336-4340)
    - Ernest Gründ; Paris (Box 660, Folder 4341-4342)
  - X346 G925, 1969 - 1971; unnumbered, 16 catalogs
    - B. R. Grüner; Amsterdam, Holland (Box 660, Folder 4343-4344)
  - X346 G945, [1911]; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - E. Guilmoto Editeur; Paris (Box 660, Folder 4345)
  - X346 G959, 1925 - 1967; nos. 1-278, 52 catalogs
    - Guntrip's Shop; Tonbridge, England (Box 660, Folder 4346-4347)
    - Guntrip's Shop; Tonbridge, England (Box 661, Folder 4348-4349)
  - X346 G96, 1952 - 1979; nos. 1-78, 54 catalogs
    - R. D. Gurney LTD.; London (Box 661, Folder 4350-4353)
    - R. D. Gurney LTD.; London (Box 662, Folder 4354-4359)
  - X346 G964, 1846; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Royal Gurley Co.; New York (Box 662, Folder 4360)
  - X346 G982, 1946 - 1968; nos. 43-68, 17 catalogs
    - Gutekunst Klipstein; Bern (Box 663, Folder 4361-4365)
- H
  - X346 H113, 1951 - 1971; nos. 26-282, 141 catalogs
    - Rudolf Habelt; Bonn (Box 664, Folder 4366-4371)
    - Rudolf Habelt; Bonn (Box 665, Folder 4372-4376)
  - X346 H115, undated; nos. 3-73, 62 catalogs
    - Hachette; Paris (Box 665, Folder 4377)
    - Hachette; Paris (Box 666, Folder 4378-4383)
    - Hachette; Paris (Box 667, Folder 4384-4386)
  - X346 H115 I, 1955 - 1971; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - Hachette; Paris (Box 667, Folder 4387)
  - X346 H116 I, 1947 - 1982; nos. 7-35, unnumbered, 18 catalogs
    - Hacker Art Books Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 667, Folder 4388-4389)
    - Hacker Art Books Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 668, Folder 4390)
  - X346 H1295, undated; nos. 1-14, 13 catalogs
    - Halcyon Antiquariaat; Amsterdam (Box 668, Folder 4391-4393)
  - X346 H138, 1939 - 1951; nos. 101-144, 38 catalogs
    - Halewood Son; Preston (Box 668, Folder 4394-4396)
  - X346 H138 I, 1953 - 1967; nos. 2-21, unnumbered, 17 catalogs
    - Halewood Son; Preston (Box 668, Folder 4397)
    - Halewood Son; Preston (Box 669, Folder 4398)
  - X346 H143, 1929-1954; unnumbered, nos. 3- 76, 68 catalogs
    - Norman A. Hall; Newton Centre, Mass. (Box 669, Folder 4399-4404)
    - Norman A. Hall; Newton Centre, Mass. (Box 670, Folder 4405)
  - X346 H146, 1904 - 1940; nos. 32-145, 48 catalogs
    - Hall's Bookshop; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 670, Folder 4406-4410)
  - X346 H15, undated, 1916-1967; nos. 36-285, 234 catalogs
    - Bernard Halliday; Leicester (Box 670, Folder 4411)
    - Bernard Halliday; Leicester (Box 671, Folder 4412-4417)
    - Bernard Halliday; Leicester (Box 672, Folder 4418-4422)
    - Bernard Halliday; Leicester (Box 673, Folder 4423-4428)
    - Bernard Halliday; Leicester (Box 674, Folder 4429-4434)
    - Bernard Halliday; Leicester (Box 675, Folder 4435)
  - X346 H178, 1947 - 1957; nos. 4-34, 28 catalogs
    - Robert H. Hamel; New York, N. Y. (Box 675, Folder 4436-4439)
  - X346 H18, 1969 - 1971; nos. 33-49, 8 catalogs
    - Charles Hamilton; New York, N. Y. (Box 675, Folder 4440)
    - Charles Hamilton; New York, N. Y. (Box 676, Folder 4441-4442)
  - X346 H1835, undated; nos. 42-49, 7 catalogs
    - Charles Hamilton; New York, N. Y. (Box 676, Folder 4443)
  - X346 H1835 I, undated; Cat. n, 1 catalog
    - Charles Hamilton; New York, N. Y. (Box 676, Folder 4444)
  - X346 H186, undated; nos. 28-181, 153 catalogs, 1 list
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 676, Folder 4445-4448)
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 677, Folder 4449-4454)
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 678, Folder 4455-4460)
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 679, Folder 4461-4466)
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 680, Folder 4467-4472)
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 681, Folder 4473)
  - X346 H186 I, undated; nos. 2-32, 29 catalogs
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 681, Folder 4474-4476)
  - X346 H186 II, undated; nos. 1-214, 45 catalogs
    Includes duplicates
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 681, Folder 4477-4478)
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 682, Folder 4479-4484)
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 683, Folder 4485-4488)
  - X346 H186 III, undated; no. 30, 1 catalog
    - Frank Hammond; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 683, Folder 4489)
  - X346 H1917, 1954 - 1973; nos. 36-125, 48 catalogs
    - Alan Hancox; Cheltenham, England (Box 683, Folder 4490-4492)
    - Alan Hancox; Cheltenham, England (Box 684, Folder 4493-4497)
  - X346 H194, undated, 1946-1967; nos. 9-110, 81 catalogs
    - Victor Hankard; Bruxelles (Box 684, Folder 4498-4499)
    - Victor Hankard; Bruxelles (Box 685, Folder 4500-4505)
  - X346 H1958, 1957 - 1986; nos. 1-76, 34 catalogs
    - T L Hannas; Kent, England (Box 686, Folder 4506-4510)
  - X346 H21, 1823 - 1829; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - George Harding; London (Box 687, Folder 4511)
  - X346 H21 II, 1890 - 1930; nos. 2-261, 168 catalogs
    - George Harding; London (Box 687, Folder 4512-4515)
    - George Harding; London (Box 688, Folder 4516-4521)
    - George Harding; London (Box 689, Folder 4522-4527)
    - George Harding; London (Box 690, Folder 4528-4533)
  - X346 H21 III, 1930 - 1960; nos. 1-97, 98 catalogs
    - George Harding; London (Box 690, Folder 4534)
    - George Harding; London (Box 691, Folder 4535-4540)
    - George Harding; London (Box 692, Folder 4541-4546)
    - George Harding; London (Box 693, Folder 4547)
  - X346 H21 IIIa, 1958; no. 1, 1 catalog
    - George Harding; London (Box 693, Folder 4548)
  - X346 H226, 1935 - 1968; nos. 1-63, 48 catalogs, 1 list
    - John Harkness Co.; London (Box 693, Folder 4549-4552)
  - X346 H226 I, undated; no. 700, 1 catalog
    - John Harkness Co.; London (Box 693, Folder 4553)
  - X346 H231, 1906; no. 25, 1 catalog
    - W. Harold Co.; London (Box 693, Folder 4554)
  - X346 H237, 1886 - 1968; unnumbered, nos. 8-197, 109 catalogs
    Name Variant: Francis P. Harper
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 694, Folder 4555-4559)
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 695, Folder 4560-4565)
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 696, Folder 4566-4571)
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 697, Folder 4572-4577)
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 698, Folder 4578-4580)
  - X346 H237 II, 1953 - 1962; nos. 1-27, 27 catalogs
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 698, Folder 4581-4583)
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 699, Folder 4584-4585)
  - X346 H237 III, 1953 - 1984; nos. 1-239, 63 catalogs
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 699, Folder 4586-4588)
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 700, Folder 4589-4594)
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 701, Folder 4595-4600)
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 702, Folder 4601-4606)
    - Lathrop C. Harper; New York, N. Y. (Box 703, Folder 4607-4609)
  - X346 H239 I, 1872 - 1969; nos. 2-505, 316 catalogs
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 703, Folder 4610-4612)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 704, Folder 4613-4618)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 705, Folder 4619-4624)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 706, Folder 4625-4630)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 707, Folder 4631-4636)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 708, Folder 4637-4642)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 709, Folder 4643-4648)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 710, Folder 4649-4654)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 711, Folder 4655-4660)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 712, Folder 4661-4666)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 713, Folder 4667-4672)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 714, Folder 4673-4678)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 715, Folder 4679-4684)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 716, Folder 4685-4691)
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 717, Folder 4692)
  - X346 H239 II, undated; nos. 1-90, 84 catalogs
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 717, Folder 4693-4696)
  - X346 H239 III, 1927 - 1939; nos. 32-79, 35 catalogs
    - Otto Harrassowitz; Leipzig (Box 718, Folder 4697-4701)
  - X346 H239 IIIa, 1959 - 1967; nos. 45-64, 13 catalogs